treasureisland.com 2017-06-30

# Privacy Policy - Treasure Island

**TI PRIVACY POLICY**

Treasure Island, LLC ("TI") is the owner and operator of the Treasure Island Hotel and Casino in Las Vegas, Nevada, USA.  In 2009, Ruffin Acquisition, LLC, wholly owned by Phil Ruffin, purchased TI from MGM Resorts International.  Treasure Island Hotel and Casino features 2,884 guest rooms and suites, approximately 90,000 square feet of gaming space, several fine and casual dining outlets, and Mystere, the first permanent production in Las Vegas by Cirque du Soleil.  TI’s dedicated staff of employees is committed to providing an unsurpassed experience for guests.  TI supports responsible gaming and has implemented the American Gaming Association's Code of Conduct for Responsible Gaming at its properties.

We hope that you enjoy our luxurious facilities, our exciting entertainment, and our quality customer service.  Because we value your patronage and respect your privacy, we are providing you with this **TI Privacy Policy** ("Privacy Policy").  This Privacy Policy pertains to the TI websites and the TI Hotel and Casino defined below (collectively, "us" or "we").  This Privacy Policy describes how Personal Information (defined below) about you may be used and disclosed by TI in the course of business.  It also describes how you can opt-out of some uses of Personal Information.

Please review this Privacy Policy carefully.  Click here to view Frequently Asked Questions or you may contact us at [TI-General@treasureisland.com](mailto:TI-General@treasureisland.com), call (702) 894-7111, or write to Treasure Island Hotel & Casino, Attn: General Counsel / Privacy Policy, 3300 Las Vegas Blvd South, Las Vegas, NV 89109.  Users of TI Web Sites should also click here to review the Terms of Use.

**I. SCOPE OF PRIVACY POLICY**

**A. TI Web Sites & Social Media**

This Privacy Policy is applicable only to the web sites and social media pages that specifically refer to this Privacy Policy ("TI Web Sites").  It does not apply to any other web sites, including other web sites that may be owned, operated, or affiliated with TI or its parent companies or subsidiaries. 

**B. TI Hotel and Casino**

This Privacy Policy is applicable only to the Treasure Island Hotel and Casino ("TI Hotel and Casino").  It does not apply to any other resorts, casinos, or other properties that are owned, operated, or affiliated with TI or its parent companies or subsidiaries.

  **II. VISITORS OUTSIDE OF THE UNITED STATES**

The TI Web Sites are maintained on servers located in the United States, and Personal Information is also stored on computers located in the United States.  The United States may not offer a level of privacy protection for Personal Information, which includes Confidential Personal Information (defined below), as great as that offered in other jurisdictions.  Therefore, the disclosure of Personal Information pursuant to this Privacy Policy is at your own risk.  We make no representation that the practices described in this Privacy Policy are compliant with laws outside of the United States that apply to the collection, security, use and disclosure of Personal Information.  TI will use its best reasonable efforts to maintain the security of Personal Information.

**III. TYPES OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

**A. Personal Information**

"Personal Information" is information through which you can be identified.  We collect Personal Information that you provide voluntarily at TI Web Sites and the TI Hotel and Casino.  We also collect Personal Information that you provide voluntarily by e-mail, postal mail, telephone, and other means.  Personal Information that we collect through TI Web Sites may include but is not limted to your name, date of birth, postal address, e-mail address, telephone number, gender, credit card information, gaming activity, and your purchase and reservation information.  In addition to the Personal Information listed above, Personal Information that we may collect at TI Hotel and Casino includes driver’s license number and state, social security number, passport information and naturalization information.  When you complete a marker play application at any TI Web Site or the TI Hotel and Casino, we may also collect the name of your firm, your firm’s address and telephone number, your position with the firm, and banking information (including the name and address of your primary and secondary banks along with your account numbers).  Some Personal Information described above is considered "Confidential Personal Information."  Confidential Personal Information includes your name associated with one or more of the following: date of birth, credit card information, driver’s license number, state ID card, social security number, passport information and naturalization information.

Personal Information may also include your image in a live video feed that can be viewed on the TI Web Sites if you visit the TI Hotel and Casino.  We may combine Personal Information with other generally or publicly available information to help us identify your preferences or interests.  Your Personal Information may also be merged with Personal Information available from other sources, including (a) e-mail address or postal address append services; (b) credit card verification and credit services; and/or (c) other resorts, casinos, or properties that are owned, operated, or affiliated with TI or its parent companies or subsidiaries or Partners.

**B. Non-Personal Information**

"Non-Personal Information" is information about you or your activities through which you cannot be personally identified.  When you use the Internet, your web browser or client software may transmit certain information to the servers that host the web sites you visit.  The information may include the unique number assigned to your server or Internet connection, your geographic location, and your movement within and interaction with the TI Web Sites, including what pages you look at and what information you download.  When you visit TI Web Sites, our servers collect such Non-Personal Information.  We use this Non-Personal Information for a variety of purposes including to generate aggregate statistics about visitors to TI Web Sites.  In situations where it is possible to do so, Non-Personal Information may be linked to Personal Information.

**C. Information Collected Utilizing Cookie Technology**

TI Web Sites utilize a website technology known as "cookies."  A cookie is a small file that contains information sent by a web site that is saved on your hard drive by your computer’s browser.  Cookies store information that a web site may need to personalize your experience and to gather web site statistical data, such as which web pages you visit, what material you download, your Internet provider’s domain name and country, and the addresses of web sites you visited immediately before and after visiting a particular web site.  TI Web Sites use cookies to collect and store your preferences for viewing the TI Web Sites, such as whether you disable a particular function, so that you may not have to disable the same function on following visits.  The cookie information may also be used to detect and resolve web site problems and to assist with customer support concerns.

In addition, TI Web Sites utilize cookies to provide a unique identifier to your computer.  This helps us to generate statistics regarding usage of TI Web Sites, such as the percentage of repeat visitors.  In situations where TI has Personal Information, the unique identifiers may be matched with Personal Information.  In addition, when you book a reservation online to stay at the TI Hotel and Casino, the reservation or confirmation number may be stored in a cookie on our computer and in an order file generated by third party vendors that assist in processing and fulfillment of TI Hotel and Casino reservations.

To browse the Internet and TI Web Sites without using cookies, you can configure your browser to reject all cookies or to notify you when each cookie is offered so that you can accept or reject each cookie.  However, if you reject all cookies, you may not be able to conduct some transactions or use some services on TI Web Sites.

**D. Social Media Information**

When you use integrated social media features on TI Web Sites, mobile applications, or other social media web sites, we may obtain Personal Information such as your name and e-mail address.

**E. Information Collected From Partners**

We may obtain Personal Information from carefully selected business partners and other entities that direct you to, or are located at, TI Web Sites and/or the TI Hotel and Casino (collectively, "Partners").  We may use Personal Information obtained from our Partners in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.  We generally have no control over how our Partners use Personal Information they collect from or about you.  Therefore, if you provide Personal Information, including Confidential Personal Information, to our Partners, we encourage you to consult our Partners’ privacy policies for more information about their privacy protection practices.

**F. Information Collected by Other Third Parties**

Certain transactions and services offered while visiting TI Web Sites may be processed or provided by third parties under contract with us for fulfillment and other purposes.  When your Personal Information is submitted to these third parties for such purposes, we require those third parties to exercise reasonable care to protect your Personal Information and restrict the use of your Personal Information to the purposes for which it was provided.

**G. Employment Application Information**

If you [apply for a job](https://careers-treasureisland.icims.com/jobs/intro) with us, we might ask for certain Personal Information about you including, for example, your work and education history, and your profile/resume.

**IV. HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

**A. Uses by TI**

**1\. Use for Marketing Purposes**

We may use Personal Information and Non-Personal Information for our own marketing purposes, including notifying you of special promotions, offers and events via postal mail, e-mail, telephone, text messaging, and other means.  We will not permit Confidential Personal Information to be used for marketing purposes.   **If you do not want us to use your Personal Information for marketing purposes, you may opt-out of such uses by notifying us (see Section V below)**.

**2\. Use for Non-Marketing Purposes**

We may use Personal Information, including Confidential Personal Information, and Non-Personal Information for purposes unrelated to marketing, including:

    (1) responding to your inquiries, complaints and other communications;  
    (2) processing and fulfilling reservations and/or purchases and making a record of such reservations and purchases;  
    (3) contacting you for confirmation or customer service after reservations and purchases are made or after you sign up for or participate in certain activities;  
    (4) for statistical or demographic analysis;  
    (5) for tracking reservations and corresponding hotel stays generated through our affiliate program and calculating and/or auditing commissions that may be paid in relation to a hotel stay;  
    (6) to help improve TI Web Sites and services;  
    (7) to customize your experience at TI Web Sites and social media pages; and/or  
    (8) to help evaluate your [employment application](http://careers-treasureisland.icims.com/jobs/intro).

Opting-out of the use of your Personal Information for marketing purposes will not prevent your Personal Information, including Confidential Personal Information, from being used for non-marketing purposes.

**B. Sharing within TI and with Subsidiaries**

Your Personal Information and Non-Personal Information may be shared for any purpose among the TI Hotel and Casino and TI Web Sites.  Your Personal Information and Non-Personal Information may also be shared for any purpose with TI parent companies and subsidiaries not covered by this Privacy Policy, and any other resorts, casinos, or other properties that are owned, operated by or affiliated with TI or its parent companies or subsidiaries (collectively, "Affiliates").  Your Confidential Personal Information will only be shared to the extent necessary to permit TI to validate your identity for the purposes of extending credit, completing a purchase transaction, recording of gaming related activity or other legitimate non-marketing business needs.  **If you do not want your Personal Information to be shared among the TI Hotel and Casino, TI Web Sites and Affiliates for marketing purposes, you may opt-out of such sharing by notifying us (see Section V below)**.

**C. Sharing With Partners for Marketing Purposes**

We may share your Personal Information and Non-Personal Information with our Partners for joint marketing efforts, or for our Partners’ own marketing purposes.  Your Confidential Personal Information will not be shared with Partners for marketing purposes.   **If you do not want us to share your Personal Information with Partners for marketing purposes, you may opt-out of such sharing by notifying us (see Section V below)**.  When we provide Personal Information to our Partners, we require those Partners to exercise reasonable care to protect your Personal Information and restrict the use of your Personal Information to the purposes for which it was provided.  To determine how Partners use the Personal Information they collect directly from you, or about you, from sources other than TI, please consult the privacy policies of our Partners.

**D. Sharing With Partners and Other Third Parties for Non-Marketing Purposes**

Although you may request to opt-out of sharing Personal Information for marketing purposes, we reserve the right to disclose Personal Information, including Confidential Personal Information, to our Partners and other third parties for the following purposes:

    (1) if you enroll in our Responsible Gaming Program (see "Responsible Gaming Program" in Section VII. below);  
    (2) for non-marketing purposes, including reservation or purchase fulfillment;  
    (3) in the event of a transfer to a third party of all or substantially all of the assets of TI, the TI Hotel and Casino, and/or any TI Web Site;  
    (4) to comply with a court order, subpoena, search warrant or other valid legal process;  
    (5) to comply with legal, regulatory or administrative requirements of any governmental authorities;  
    (6) to protect and defend TI, its subsidiaries and affiliates, and all of their officers, directors, employees, attorneys and agents in connection with any legal action, claim or dispute;  
    (7) to satisfy any contractual obligation to indemnify its contractors, Partners or other third parties in connection with any legal action, claim or dispute;  
    (8) to enforce the Terms of Use of TI Web Sites;  
    (9) to prevent imminent physical harm or threats to public safety;  
    (10) to third party vendors that TI may use to perform functions on behalf of TI, such as companies that process credit card transactions;  
    (11) to prevent fraud; and  
    (12) to engage in debt collection.

When we provide Personal Information to our Partners and other third parties for such purposes, we require those Partners and third parties to exercise reasonable care to protect your Personal Information and restrict the use of your Personal Information to the purposes for which it was provided.    

**V. YOUR COMMUNICATION PREFERENCES**

**A. Establishing a Preference Account**

We are committed to protecting the accuracy and confidentiality of your Personal Information and encourage you to tell us how you want us to communicate with you and let you know about special offers.  By creating a TI Preference Account, you can view and update your Personal Information and chose your communication preferences.  Your Preference Account gives you the ability to select from communications preference options including direct mail, e-mail, telemarketing, and text messaging.

To create a Preference Account, or to update your preferences at any time after you have created your Preference Account, visit the [TI Web Site](http://www.treasureisland.com/) and select "[Email Promotions](https://app.streamsend.com/public/IKGY/asC/subscribe)" or "MyTI Guestbook".   These options will allow you to create and access your Preference Account.

If you are a casino member of TI Players Club, you may update your communications preferences by logging in to your online account, and selecting "Update" on Your Member Home Page.  Information regarding opt-out procedures is also provided within every TI promotional e-mail or direct mail communication sent to you.

**B. How to Opt-Out**

If you wish to opt-out of receiving solicitations from us, or do not want us to share your Personal Information with Partners, for marketing purposes, you can record your preferences by emailing us at [TI-General@treasureisland.com](mailto:TI-General@treasureisland.com), call (702-894-7111), or write to:

Treasure Island Hotel & Casino  
Attn: Privacy Policy  
3300 Las Vegas Boulevard South  
Las Vegas, Nevada 89109

If you do not want us to share your Personal Information among the TI Hotel and Casino and TI Web Sites or Affiliates for marketing purposes, you may email us at [TI-General@treasureisland.com](mailto:TI-General@treasureisland.com), or call (702) 894-7111.

**C. Telemarketing**

Although you may have registered your telephone number on a Federal or State do not call list, certain exemptions (for example, for communicating with established customers) may allow us to contact you via telephone. However, to ensure our customer’s preferences are honored, we also maintain our own internal "Do Not Call" list.  If you would like to opt-out of receiving telemarketing sales calls from us by adding your telephone number to our internal Do Not Call list, you may email us at [TI-General@treasureisland.com](mailto:TI-General@treasureisland.com), or call (702) 894-7111.

**D. California, USA  Privacy Policy Rights**

To fulfill the intent of the State of California law requiring web sites to conspicuously post their privacy policies, we have included the following summary.  The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to identify the Personal Information we collect, describe how you can review and make changes to that Personal Information, describe how you can learn about changes to the Privacy Policy, and provide you with a mechanism to opt-out of certain marketing activities. you wish to opt-out of receiving solicitations from us, or do not want us to share your Personal Information with Partners for marketing purposes, you may email us at [TI-General@treasureisland.com](mailto:TI-General@treasureisland.com), call (702) 894-7111, or write to:

Treasure Island Hotel & Casino  
Attn: Privacy Policy  
3300 Las Vegas Boulevard South  
Las Vegas, Nevada 89109

If you do not want us to share your Personal Information among the TI Hotel and Casino and TI Web Sites or Affiliates for marketing purposes, you may email us at [TI-General@treasureisland.com](mailto:TI-General@treasureisland.com) or call (702) 894-7111.

**VI. SECURITY**

Non-Personal Information and Personal Information, including Confidential Personal Information, collected by the TI Web Sites and the TI Hotel and Casino is stored on secure servers.  The secure servers are protected by firewalls and a multitude of other industry standard security measures.  These security measures are instituted to ensure the protection of these secure servers from unauthorized access.  However, no security system is impenetrable, and these systems could become accessible in the event of a security breach.  We have controls in place that are designed to detect potential data breaches, contain and minimize the loss of data, and conduct forensic investigations of a breach.

Our staff is required to take reasonable measures to ensure that unauthorized persons cannot view or access your Personal Information.  Employees who violate our privacy policies are subject to disciplinary action, up to and including termination.

We cannot enforce or control the security of the computers, electronic devices, or electronic communication method that a consumer may utilize to send e-mails and submit information to us over the Internet.  You are responsible for ensuring that the computers, electronic devices and electronic communication methods you utilize will provide adequate security for communicating with us.  We are not responsible for the disclosure or interception of your information before we receive it.

As a standard security practice, we will take reasonable steps, which are standard in the industry to ensure that the communication methods used to support the TI Web Sites do not permit connection or communication by methods that have known security weaknesses or vulnerabilities.  As such, if you experience trouble using a TI Web Site, it may be an indication that you need to upgrade your Internet browsing tool or application to a newer version that supports more secure communication methods.    

**VII. RESPONSIBLE GAMING PROGRAM**

We believe that gaming should always be handled responsibly.  That is why TI adheres to the [American Gaming Association Code of Conduct for Responsible Gaming](https://www.americangaming.org/about/code-of-conduct).  As part of our Responsible Gaming Program, we will not use the Personal Information of members of the TI Self-Limit Access Program of Nevada, as applicable, for any marketing purposes, including direct mail marketing, telemarketing, promotional mail, and player recognition programs.

**VIII. CONNECTIONS (LINKS) TO THIRD PARTY WEB SITES**

When you connect (link) to unaffiliated third-party sites, including sites operated by our Partners, through the TI Web Sites, we are not responsible for, and cannot control the information collection or privacy practices of those sites.

It is important that you review and understand the privacy policies posted on any linked sites you visit, before providing any Personal Information.  These sites may also collect cookies, or allow third-party advertisers on their sites to collect cookies.  You can often find information regarding a site and its privacy policy (if one exists) on the site’s home page.  If you cannot find a site’s privacy policy or do not like a site’s privacy policy, you may prefer not to conduct business with, nor provide information through, that site.

**IX. PERSONS UNDER AGES 18 AND 21**

Certain areas and activities at the TI Hotel and Casino and TI Web Sites are intended for use only by persons 21 years of age or older.

If you are under the age of 21, we ask that you do not access or attempt to access any portions of the Web Sites that are restricted to persons age 21 or older, including but not limited to any Web Sites containing password-restricted information (see TI Terms of Use for more information).

We reserve the right to verify your age at any time for any reason and may refuse admittance or service to a person who does not have valid age identification at any time.

TI abides by the [Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act](https://www.ftc.gov/enforcement/rules/rulemaking-regulatory-reform-proceedings/childrens-online-privacy-protection-rule) (COPPA).  Therefore, we do not knowingly collect or allow the collection of Personal Information from persons under the age of 18.  If the parent or guardian of a person under 18 believes that the person has provided us with Personal Information, the parent or guardian of that person should contact us at [TI-General@treasureisland.com](mailto:TI-General@treasureisland.com) and request that such Personal Information be deleted from our files.  If a person under the age of 18 submits Personal Information, we delete the information as soon as we discover the source of the submission, and we do not use the information for any purpose.

**X. CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

We reserve the right to revise this Privacy Policy at any time without notice.  When this Privacy Policy is revised the revised Privacy Policy will be available at the TI Hotel and Casino and will be posted on the TI Web Sites. Any revised Privacy Policy will only apply prospectively to Personal Information or Non Personal Information collected or modified after the effective date of the revised policy.  You should periodically review the Privacy Policy available at the TI Hotel and Casino and the TI Web Sites for revisions.  You are encouraged to bookmark the Web Sites to check for updates and take or print out copies of the Privacy Policy for your records.  Use of a TI Web Site after revision of the Privacy Policy signifies your consent to the revised Privacy Policy.

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [TI-General@treasureisland.com](mailto:TI-General@treasureisland.com).

Last Revised: February 2017

© Treasure Island, LLC
